<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://hammes.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 Sep 2018 22:16:25 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://hammes.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Flourless Peanut Butter/Chocolate Chip Cookies</title>
      <link>http://hammes.io/recipes/flourless-peanut-butter-cookies/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Sep 2018 22:16:25 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://hammes.io/recipes/flourless-peanut-butter-cookies/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  1 cup smooth peanut butter &amp;frac34; cup brown sugar &amp;frac12; tsp baking soda Pinch of salt 1 large egg 1 tsp vanilla extract &amp;frac12; cup chocolate chips  Directions  Preheat oven to 350 °F.
 Beat the peanut butter, sugar, baking soda, and salt together until well-blended.
 Add the egg and vanilla and mix until incorporated.
 Stir in the chocolate chips.
 Scoop the dough by the tablespoonful onto a parchment-lined baking sheet and push the top of the dough to flatten just slightly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Greek Lemon Chicken and Potatoes</title>
      <link>http://hammes.io/recipes/greek-lemon-chicken-and-potatoes/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 18:11:53 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://hammes.io/recipes/greek-lemon-chicken-and-potatoes/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  4 lb bone-in skin-on chicken thighs 3 russet potatoes, quartered and peeled 1 tbsp kosher salt 1 tsp black pepper 1 tsp dried rosemary 1 rounded tbsp dried oregano Pinch of cayenne 6 cloves of garlic, freshly minced &amp;frac12; cup fresh lemon juice (approximately 3 lemons) &amp;frac12; cup olive oil 2/3 cup chicken broth (for deglazing) Freshly chopped oregano to garnish  Directions  Put the chicken into a mixing bowl.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Basic Chili</title>
      <link>http://hammes.io/recipes/basic-chili/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 17:31:39 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://hammes.io/recipes/basic-chili/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  2 tbsp olive oil 1 yellow onion, diced 2 cloves garlic, minced 1 lb ground beef 15 oz can kidney beans 15 oz can black beans 15 oz can diced tomatoes 6 oz can tomato paste 1 cup beef broth (or water)  Chili Seasoning
 1 tbsp chili powder 1 tsp ground cumin &amp;frac14; tsp cayenne pepper &amp;frac14; tsp garlic powder &amp;frac12; tsp onion powder &amp;frac12; tbsp brown sugar 1 tsp salt &amp;frac12; tsp ground pepper  Directions  Cook the onions over medium heat until translucent.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Asian Cabbage Stir Fry</title>
      <link>http://hammes.io/recipes/asian-cabbage-stir-fry/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Sep 2018 14:15:18 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://hammes.io/recipes/asian-cabbage-stir-fry/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients Stir fry sauce:
 2 tbsp soy sauce 1 tbsp toasted sesame oil 1 tbsp sriracha &amp;frac12; tbsp brown sugar  Stir fry:
 &amp;frac12; head green cabbage, shredded &amp;frac12; tbsp neutral cooking oil &amp;frac12; lb lean ground beef 2 cloves garlic, minced 1 knob ginger Pinch of salt &amp;amp; pepper 2 carrots, shredded (optional) 3 green onions, sliced diagonally (optional)  Garnishes:
 1 tbsp sesame seeds (optional) 1 tbsp sriracha (optional)  Directions  Heat a large skillet over medium heat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>French Toast</title>
      <link>http://hammes.io/recipes/french-toast/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2018 20:13:38 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://hammes.io/recipes/french-toast/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  1 cup half-and-half 3 large eggs 2 tablespoons honey &amp;frac14; teaspoon salt 3 (&amp;frac12; inch) slices day-old or stale country loaf Butter to grease pan  Directions  In a medium-size mixing bowl, whisk together the half-and-half, eggs, honey, and salt. This may be done the night before.
 Preheat oven to 375° F.
 Dip the slices of bread into the custard and allow to soak for 30 seconds on each side.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Black Bean Quesadillas</title>
      <link>http://hammes.io/recipes/black-bean-quesadillas/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2017 00:21:10 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://hammes.io/recipes/black-bean-quesadillas/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  1 15 oz. can black beans 1 cup frozen corn kernels &amp;frac12; small red onion 1 clove garlic &amp;frac14; bunch fresh cilantro 2 cups shredded cheese 1 batch taco seasoning 10 taco-sized tortillas  Directions  Drain the can of beans and rinse lightly. Place the beans in a large bowl along with the corn (no need to thaw).
 Rinse the cilantro, remove the leaves, and chop roughly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Toasted Honey Popcorn</title>
      <link>http://hammes.io/recipes/toasted-honey-popcorn/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2017 09:42:16 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://hammes.io/recipes/toasted-honey-popcorn/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  2 tsp unflavored oil &amp;frac12; cup popcorn kernels 4 tbsp (&amp;frac12; stick) unsalted butter 3 tbsp honey 1 tsp kosher salt  Directions  Place the oil and three popcorn kernels in a large pot. Cover and heat over medium heat until all three kernels have popped. Pour in the remaining kernels, cover the pot again, and shake to distribute. As the popcorn pops, shake occasionally. Immediately remove from heat once the popping slows to two or three seconds between pops.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tempo Swing Thanksgiving 2017</title>
      <link>http://hammes.io/temposwing-thanksgiving-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2017 15:09:24 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://hammes.io/temposwing-thanksgiving-2017/</guid>
      <description>TL;DR  C Jam Blues - Lincoln Center Jazz Orchestra Sixteen Tons - Tennessee Ernie Ford In The Mood - Glenn Miller Ain&amp;rsquo;t No Mountain High Enough - Ashford &amp;amp; Simpson Bei Mir Bist Du Schöen - Janis Siegel  C Jam Blues Parfois, la simplicité est la meilleure qualité qu&amp;rsquo;une chanson peut espère avoir. Avec une mélodie qui ne compte que deux tones uniques, C Jam Blues fourni une plateforme stable qui n&amp;rsquo;interfère pas avec des danses créatives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Québec DJ</title>
      <link>http://hammes.io/temposwing-halloween-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2017 11:42:26 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://hammes.io/temposwing-halloween-2017/</guid>
      <description>La liste résumée, sans ordre particulier :
 My Baby Just Cares For Me - Nina Simone The Lion Sleeps Tonight - The Tokens Fairytale - Sara Bareilles Frantonality - Erroll Garner  My Baby Just Cares For Me - Nina Simone Une de mes chansons favorites ; une mélodie lente et calme, parfaite pour se relaxer plus tard pendant la soirée.
 The Lion Sleeps Tonight - The Tokens Pas une chanson de &amp;ldquo;swing&amp;rdquo; traditionel, mais elle offre plusieurs opportunités à des danseurs de montrer leur créativité et leur musicalité.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coconut Macaroons</title>
      <link>http://hammes.io/recipes/coconut-macaroons/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2017 13:27:54 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://hammes.io/recipes/coconut-macaroons/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  3 cups sweetened, shredded coconut 4 large egg whites &amp;frac12; cup sugar 1 teaspoon vanilla or almond extract &amp;frac14; teaspoon salt  Directions  Preheat the oven to 350°F For deeper coconut flavor and extra-crispy macaroons, spread the coconut on the baking sheet and toast for about 5 minutes, or until just barely starting to show some color. Let cool slightly before using. Combine the egg whites, sugar, vanilla, and salt in a mixing bowl.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Butter Frosting</title>
      <link>http://hammes.io/recipes/butter-frosting/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Dec 2016 13:28:25 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://hammes.io/recipes/butter-frosting/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  6 tbsp butter 4 &amp;frac12; cups sifted confectioners&amp;rsquo; sugar (approximate) &amp;frac14; cup milk 1 tsp vanilla extract &amp;frac12; tsp almond extract Food coloring (optional)  Directions  In a bowl beat butter or margarine until fluffy. Gradually add 2 cups of the sugar, beating well. Beat in the milk, vanilla, and almond Alternate adding sugar and beating until a good spreading consistency is reached. Tint with food coloring if desired.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sugar Cookies</title>
      <link>http://hammes.io/recipes/sugar-cookies/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Dec 2016 13:28:16 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://hammes.io/recipes/sugar-cookies/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  1 &amp;frac12; cup butter, softened 2 cups white sugar 4 eggs 1 teaspoon vanilla extract 1 teaspoon almond extract (optional) 5 cups flour 2 teaspoon baking powder 1 teaspoon salt  Directions  In a large bowl, cream together butter and sugar until smooth. Beat in eggs and vanilla. Stir in the flour, baking powder, and salt. Cover, and chill dough for at least one hour. Preheat oven to 350 degrees.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Honey Cornbread Muffins</title>
      <link>http://hammes.io/recipes/honey-cornbread-muffins/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2016 21:40:51 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://hammes.io/recipes/honey-cornbread-muffins/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>No-Bake Cookies</title>
      <link>http://hammes.io/recipes/no-bake-cookies/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2016 21:40:39 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://hammes.io/recipes/no-bake-cookies/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  2 cups sugar &amp;frac12; cup milk 1 stick (8 tablespoons) unsalted butter &amp;frac14; cup unsweetened cocoa powder 3 cups old-fashioned rolled oats 1 cup smooth peanut butter 1 tablespoon pure vanilla extract Large pinch kosher salt  Directions Line two baking sheets with wax paper or parchment.
Bring the sugar, milk, butter and cocoa to a boil in a medium saucepan over medium heat, stirring occasionally, then let boil for 1 minute.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chocolate Peppermint Snaps</title>
      <link>http://hammes.io/recipes/chocolate-peppermint-snaps/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2016 21:40:27 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://hammes.io/recipes/chocolate-peppermint-snaps/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  &amp;frac34; cup (12 tablespoons) unsalted butter &amp;frac12; cup brown sugar &amp;frac12; cup granulated sugar 1 large egg 1 teaspon vanilla extract 1 teaspoon peppermint extract, or 1/8 teaspoon peppermint oil (or to taste) 1 &amp;frac12; cups all-purpose flour &amp;frac14; cup cocoa powder 1 teaspoon baking soda &amp;frac14; teaspoon salt 1 cup semisweet chocolate chips  Directions  Preheat the oven to 350°F. Lightly grease (or line with parchment) two baking sheets.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>